

# **ABOUT ME**

Developing is my passion. I'm an energetic and passionate website developer. I have over 4 years of experience in web and WordPress page designing and also developing. I am very open-minded, flexible and can give you valuable suggestion which greatly helps your brand to succeed.

# **MY CONTACT**

#### Home:

+880 17511-56833

#### **Email:**

syber.suprio@gmail.com

#### **Social Media:**

@suprio\_pramanik

## Website:

www.sybertm05.evalycart.com/mp

#### **Address:**

LinkRoad, Cox's Bazar, Bangladesh Hello, Everyone

# **SUPRIO PRAMANIK**

# WEB DEVELOPER

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Web Developer**

UTC Labs
July 2018 to present

- Built enterprise-level web applications
- Improved codes to automate other tasks

## **Frontend Development**

Frontend Inc. Aug 2016 to April 2018

- Assisted in developing the company's website
- Provided ongoing maintenance

#### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

#### **Coding Languages:**

C#, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Python, PHP

## Frameworks/Systems:

AngularJS, Bootstrap, Visual Studio, Team Foundation Server, Sublime Text

#### **EDUCATIONAL TRAINING**

## Cox's Bazar - Institute

Diploma in Computer Technology

- Enrolled since Sept. 2018 to present
- Taking up specialization courses in web design to broaden skill set